I'm sitting here like 10 seconds from
the last video
people get a little bit lost because it
I di did me pop into my head like I'm
not as inspired and feeling like I need
to do all hunderd by the end of today
because I did over 50 just yesterday and
so one I need to be kind to myself
because if I only have ten ideas today
that's okay and I think I'm already over
10 90s today but in even just
acknowledging that I was able to come up
with am because I was like what about my
inspiration meter is down and I think
that is a pen but if you play The Sims I
played like the first version of The
Sims a little bit of a second and you
have your little your little bars that
tell you that your people are hungry or
tired thirsty that they don't have
enough social contact and I think having
that in real life would actually be
really helpful so I don't know how it
would work I don't think I would
actually able to test you but like hey
you haven't eaten in a while maybe you
should go eat how about eating this
delicious thing in your fridge and you
haven't had human interaction in a while
huh phone you call a friend we were
calling them for you right now
just a Sims bar simulator in real life
and help with it being full is Apple
number 62